<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="300dp"
    android:layout_height="600dp"
    android:layout_gravity="center"
    android:background="@drawable/dialog_bg">

    <FrameLayout
        android:id="@+id/frameLayout3"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="horizontal">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/textView36"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="50dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:text="Terms and Conditions"
            android:textColor="#8a000000"
            android:textSize="17sp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/dialogcls"
            android:layout_width="20dp"
            android:layout_height="20dp"

            android:layout_gravity="right"
            android:layout_marginStart="15dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="15dp"
            android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
            android:layout_marginEnd="10dp"
            app:srcCompat="@drawable/close_icon" />
    </FrameLayout>

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/frameLayout3"
        tools:layout_editor_absoluteY="50dp">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView20"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginStart="5dp"
                android:layout_marginLeft="5dp"
                android:layout_marginTop="5dp"
                android:layout_marginEnd="5dp"
                android:layout_marginRight="5dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="20dp"
                android:text="1.PROPERTY OF THE APP\n\n The property of the app,, Health and Fitness mobile application belongs to: Health and Fitness, S.L., located Soldevanahalli, Hesaraghatta Main Road, Bengaluru, India with an engineering group project demo.\n\n The General Terms of Use and Privacy Policy governing the use of the services offered through the S.L. (Health and Fitness app, “us”, “we”) app (the “Service” or “Services”), the use of Health and Fitness mobile application (“Application”) through mobile devices that enables you to have access to the Internet, the conditions of processing personal data provided by you through the use of our Application, and the relationships between you (Users), and Health and Fitness app.\n\n Subject to your acceptance of and adherence to these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, Health and Fitness app hereby grants you a limited, non-exclusive license to utilize the Health and Fitness app Services as set forth herein. The terms “you” and “user” shall refer to all individuals and entities that access or utilize the Health and Fitness app Services.\n\n Services are only available to registered Users and HCP. By your affirmative actions of using  the Application, as applicable, the User and the HCP expressly consent to and accept the General Terms of Use and Privacy Policy contained herein.\n\n \n 2. DISCLAIMER OF THE PLATFORM\n\n Health and Fitness app is a platform, which connects the Users to their own specific lifestyle changes to become a fit member of society. The information shared by the users may contain Health-related information and personal data information. However, Health and Fitness app, S.L. does not own any of such data or information. Therefore, Health and Fitness app, S.L. cannot be held liable for any event occurred relating to such data.\n\n \n 3. REGISTRATION PROCESS\n\n In accordance with the provisions of the law governing these General Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy, access to the Health and Fitness app Services is limited to persons over 14 years of age. If you are under 14 we will require you prior to use, expressly, to secure authorization in writing from your parents or guardians. Therefore, when registering on Health and Fitness app Services, you expressly state and ensure that you fulfil this requirement and otherwise accept the consequences if they arise. If you are unable to comply with the conditions laid down in this paragraph, please do not register at Health and Fitness app.\n\n \n 4.HOW DO WE WORK?\n\n Once registration is completed by the User, Health and Fitness app works through the  mobile devices where the Application has been downloaded and installed. By registering as a User you will allow Health and Fitness app to use your data once it has been dissociated from you, and it cannot be associated with you as you always remain anonymous along with the aggregated anonymous data from other registered Users. Also, the User registration will allow you to synchronize your data in a secure environment to make and keep a backup copy so you can store and retrieve your data at any time and from any device that lets you do so.\n\n \n 5.MODIFICATIONS TO THE TERMS OF USE\n\n We may make changes to the Terms of Use from time to time. A link to the most current Terms of Use will be available on the home page of the Health and Fitness app and we will indicate the date of the “Latest Update” at the bottom of the Terms of Use. You are held responsible to visit this page periodically to review the most current Terms of Use. Your continued use of the Health and Fitness app Services following the posting of such changes constitutes your acceptance of the amended Terms of Use.\n\n After incorporation of the new content in the General Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, the User shall declare to have read and accepted the new content and all its content.\n\n In case of modification, change or termination of any of the content in these General Terms and Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy under sentence or judgment given by a competent court or under an award made by an arbitrator or by a court of arbitration, the other content that have not been modified, changed, or resolved remain in force and shall be valid for both parties.\n\n \n 6.PRECAUTIONS\n\n Health and Fitness app provides mobile platforms so individuals can self-monitor their recovery progress. However, it does not provide any legal, medical, or psychological advice, diagnoses, or treatment. Therefore, you assume full risk and responsibility for your use of information obtained through the Health and Fitness app Services.\n\n You acknowledge that all of the information and content in the Health and Fitness app Services is for informational purposes only.\n\n You are not a patient or client of Health and Fitness app. You must contact a professional for medical, legal, or psychological advice. If you think you may have a medical emergency, call your doctor or emergency phone number immediately.\n\n \n 7. OWNERSHIP OF THE HEALTH AND FITNESS APP SERVICES\n\n Health and Fitness app owns or has rights to all of the content in the Health and Fitness Services, excluding User Health-Related Information, which belongs exclusively to the User.\n\n The contents of the Health and Fitness app Services include: designs, text, graphics, images, video, information, logos, button icons, software, audio files, computer code, and other Health and Fitness app content. All Health and Fitness app Content and the compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement, and assembly) of all Health and Fitness Services Content are the property of Health and Fitness app, S.L. or its licensors and are protected under copyright. For this reason, the User shall refrain from reproducing, adapting, combining or integrating into other applications, arranging or otherwise handling or transforming, and from publicly communicating or publishing the Health and Fitness app Content.\n\n Health and Fitness app is committed to respecting the rights of industrial and intellectual property of others and expects Users to act in a similar manner.\n\n According to the law in effect at the time, Health and Fitness app responds promptly to claims for infringement on industrial or intellectual property rights that are allegedly committed by Users on the Health and Fitness app. Such claims shall, where appropriate, be notified to the appropriate authorities.\n\n \n 8.WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT?\n\n “Personal Information” for the purposes of this policy means information that identifies you, such as your name, address, phone number, fax number or email address. We do not consider Personal Information to include information that has been anonymized. We collect Personal Information when you:\n\n communicate with us through customer support\n\n communicate with us by sending a feature request.\n\n \n 9.CHILDREN\n\n We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 14. If we discover that a child under the age of 14 has provided us with personally identifying information, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.\n\n \n 10.UPDATES TO THIS POLICY\n\n We may update this Policy periodically. The date last revised appears at the bottom of the Policy. Changes take effect immediately upon posting.\n\n \n 11. DATA SECURITY\n\n Despite the fact that Health and Fitness app, S.L. does not process or store the data shared by the Users. Health and Fitness ensures absolute confidentiality and privacy of our Users  personal data, and has therefore adopted essential security measures to prevent alteration, loss, treatment or unauthorized access to guarantee its integrity and safety, and has especially taken the measures provided.\n\n \n 12.GOVERNING LAW AND JURISDICTION\n\n The General Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy shall be governed by Indian law prevalent at the time. Any dispute arising from use of the Application by the User or any, as well as any issues that may arise concerning the interpretation, application and enforcement of these General Terms of Use or the Privacy Policy shall be submitted to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of the City of Bengaluru (India).\n\n \n 13.CONTACT US IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS\n\n If you have questions, comments, concerns or feedback regarding this Policy or any other privacy or security concern, send an e-mail to our senior developers:\n\n \n 1.Kush Raj Singh (kushsingh01230@gmail.com)\n\n 2.Harshit Karn (harshitsma2011@gmail.com)\n\n 3.Aswini Verma (aswinir.18.becs@acharya.ac.in)\n\n \n Date of last revision of the General Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy: July 14, 2021\n\n \n"
                android:textColor="#8a000000" />
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>